<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DigiSafran</string>
    <string name="selected_language">English</string>

    <string-array name="styles">
        <item>Standard</item>
        <item>Silver</item>
        <item>Retro</item>
        <item>Dark</item>
        <item>Night</item>
        <item>Aubergine</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="videoOptions">
        <item>External app</item>
        <item>In app</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="languages">
        <item>English</item>
        <item>Türkçe</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="satellite">Switch to satellite view</string>
    <string name="options">Options</string>
    <string name="exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="ttsText">Text to speech</string>
    <string name="langDefault">English</string>
    <string name="videoDefault">In app</string>


<!--    START HERE-->
    <string-array name="geofenceLocations">
<!--        konak-->
        <item>41.2455071</item>
        <item>32.6905126</item>
<!--        cinci han-->
        <item>41.2452793</item>
        <item>32.6919672</item>
<!--        tabakhane-->
        <item>41.2424884</item>
        <item>32.6888444</item>
<!--        yemeniciler-->
        <item>41.2448288</item>
        <item>32.6901181</item>
<!--        demirciler-->
        <item>41.2440873</item>
        <item>32.6909086</item>
        <!--    köprülü camii -->
        <item>41.2447139</item>
        <item>32.6930467</item>
        <!--    eski belediye -->
        <item>41.2446698</item>
        <item>32.6931054</item>
<!--        cam teras -->
        <item>41.2795113</item>
        <item>32.6825606</item>
        <!--        ulu camii -->
        <item>41.2483648</item>
        <item>32.685976</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="geofenceTitles">
        <item>Safranbolu Historical Government House</item>
        <item>Cinci Han</item>
        <item>Tabakhane Museum</item>
        <item>Yemeniciler Arasta</item>
        <item>Blacksmiths\' Arasta</item>
        <item>Koprulu Mehmet Pasha Mosque</item>
        <item>Old Town Hall</item>
        <item>Crystal Glass Terrace</item>
        <item>Ulu Mosque - St. Stefan Church</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="videos">
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
        <item>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VYawF7ck1Z8</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="details">
<!--        konak-->
        <item>
            Safranbolu Historical Government Mansion, which was built on the hill called the castle between 1904-1906, was used as a government mansion until 19 January 1976 and became unusable as a result of a fire that broke out on that date.
            Restoration work started in 2000 by the Ministry of Culture and was completed in 2006 and opened to service as the City History Museum.
            In the building, which is currently used as a museum, the entrance is paid and has 2 floors. On the lower floor, there are historical artifacts used by the people in Safranbolu, old pictures of Safranbolu, old manuscripts. On the upper floor, there is the office room and various artifacts. In the basement, the cellar, different tradesmen\'s branches are introduced with the materials they use, wax sculptures and pictures.
        </item>
<!--        cinci han-->
        <item>
            Cinci Inn was built by Karabaşzade Hüseyin Efendi (Cinci Hoca) from Safranbolu in 1645. Cinci Inn, which was used as a caravanserai until the 20th century, when the historical Silk Road began to lose its effectiveness, was used as a warehouse by Safranbolu tradesmen since the beginning of the 20th century, then after the necessary restoration, this place serves both as a hotel and a restaurant.
            The lower floor porticos with pointed arches resting on the piers in the inn are covered with barrel vaults on both sides of the entrance and in front of the toilets on the opposite façade, and with cross vaults on the other parts. There are rooms behind the porticoes and except for the ones in the corners, these rooms open to the porticoes with a window and door.
            There is a hearth and a niche inside the rooms, all of which are covered with barrel vaults. In the middle of the rectangular courtyard, there is an eleven-cornered pool, which was built later, which is understood to be octagonal originally.
            Behind the portico covered with a barrel vault opposite the entrance and 7 m. The section at the end of the long hall is divided into lavatories covered with barrel vaults.
            Behind the portico to the right of the entrance are barns and warehouses. With its 300-meter underground tunnel, it is located on a large canyon where the city\'s wastewater and sewers are disciplined.
            The infrastructure project of this inn lasted for 20 years. The building is 23.50 × 11.50 m. It was built according to a two-storey portico order surrounding a rectangular courtyard. While the inn was being built, a bath and a tannery were built next to it, thinking that it would improve Safranbolu.
        </item>
<!--        tabak-->
        <item>
            It is Turkey\'s first and only excursion tannery in Safranbolu, which has a history of 800 years and has survived from nearly 200 tanneries. People used primitive methods to turn animal hides into leather in order to meet their basic needs such as covering and protection from the cold, and this has played an important role in the development of leatherwork over time.
        </item>
<!--        yemeniciler-->
        <item>
            Yemeniciler Arasta The Safranbolu Yemeniciler Bazaar Arasta, which is located in Safranbolu and consists of 48 wooden shops adjacent to each other, is one of the historical places of the region. Adjacent to Köprülü Mehmet Pasha Mosque is the old Guild Bazaar where shoes called “yemeni” are made. The restored bazaar is used for touristic purposes.
        </item>
<!--        demirciler-->
        <item>
            Blacksmiths\' Arastasi Blacksmithing is a traditional profession and craft, which is part of handicrafts whose raw material is metal, and is based on processing and shaping the iron mine with the help of simple hand tools. It is the only living guild bazaar where blacksmithing handicrafts are produced. Coppersmiths and tinsmiths also work in this bazaar.
        </item>
        <!-- Köprülü camii-->
        <item>
            Köprülü Mehmet Pasha Mosque was built in 1661 by Mehmet Pasha. The mosque, which was previously restored in 1970 and 1995, was restored in 2019.\n\n
            There is a large arched door at the entrance of the courtyard of the mosque. In the building located in the courtyard of the mosque, there is a fountain, a timetable, a library and a sundial. There are 95 Ottoman sundials and one is the sundial in Mehmet Pasha Mosque with a bridge.\n\n
            The Köprülü Mehmet Pasha Mosque continues to be built among the people. In the story, the practice and fulfillment of the Ottoman Grand Vizier Köprülü Mehmet Pasha\'s training to be built in a mosque instead of the dervish lodge where he prayed for the first time in Safranbolu.
        </item>
        <!-- Eski Belediye-->
        <item>
            The Old Town Hall is located in the Old Bazaar next to historical monuments such as Köprülü Mehmet Pasha Mosque and Cinci Han. It was built by Refik Güler in 1922.
        </item>
        <!-- Kristal cam teras-->
        <item>
            Crystal Glass Terrace was built on Tokatlı Canyon. Its width is 11 meters, while its height is 80 meters. The glass terrace, which can carry an average of 75 tons of weight, consists of 3 glasses of 3 cm thickness.\n\n
            It has an area of approximately 100 square meters. The Crystal Glass Terrace has a simultaneous carrying limit of 400 people, but 30 people are allowed during the trip.\n\n
            Thanks to the cafe located above the Crystal Glass Terrace, it is also possible to drink tea and coffee with the view.
        </item>
        <!-- Ulu camii-->
        <item>
            St. Stephen\'s Church, which remained from the Greeks, was built as a church in 1872 and converted into a mosque in 1956 and its name was changed to Ulu Mosque.\n\n
            Inside the building, there is an inscription written in Greek alphabet that witnessed the construction time. In this inscription, Queen Eudokia mentions that she got rid of the pain in her leg and that she built a church in the city of Theodor on April 8, 515.\n\n
            Based on the city\'s old name of Theodoroupolis, there are rumors that Theodor was a Governor or an Ionian princess, although the clarity is not clear.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="gridImages">
        <item>@drawable/konak1</item>
        <item>@drawable/han0</item>
        <item>@drawable/tabak1</item>
        <item>@drawable/yemeniciler1</item>
        <item>@drawable/demirciler1</item>
        <item>@drawable/koprulu1</item>
        <item>@drawable/eskibel1</item>
        <item>@drawable/camteras1</item>
        <item>@drawable/ulucamii1</item>
    </array>
    <array name="placeImages">
        <item>@array/konak</item>
        <item>@array/cinci_hani</item>
        <item>@array/tabak</item>
        <item>@array/yemeniciler</item>
        <item>@array/demirciler</item>
        <item>@array/koprulu</item>
        <item>@array/eskibel</item>
        <item>@array/camteras</item>
        <item>@array/ulucamii</item>
    </array>
    <array name="highResPlaceImages">
        <item>@array/konakH</item>
        <item>@array/cinci_haniH</item>
        <item>@array/tabakH</item>
        <item>@array/yemenicilerH</item>
        <item>@array/demircilerH</item>
        <item>@array/kopruluH</item>
        <item>@array/eskibelH</item>
        <item>@array/camterasH</item>
        <item>@array/ulucamiiH</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="konak">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/zcpAnbr.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/RQk6pCg.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/QdsIpcC.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/oPAdToH.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/7j9hjoL.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/466sKt1.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/P78LlEp.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/Yvz8oZD.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/OyI7HCs.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="konakH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/jIGIFSi.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/DUuDySG.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/8lGBXHL.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/zt8cZZe.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/gBbslAY.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/rPMBO85.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/JThovHZ.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/4XsDOMC.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/CUqIVdF.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cinci_hani">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/FyRmeep.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/PFjoYrW.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/OHQFAew.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/gJiibRM.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/33ZQNau.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/ZerGqtl.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/GKXf47j.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/Pe7B3Uk.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/cAZdEtB.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/1jt70Wm.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/vm7J0IU.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/srgN5wD.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/VepKwtD.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cinci_haniH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/73YYO4m.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/13Tp1qC.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/21O0KSR.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/I6IPNmv.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/foCnh5O.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/4n2408S.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/Bsmtbnq.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/q3rhfRj.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/qKioJhc.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/8VgDpdK.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/OJUJzP8.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/UaAt5zO.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/weHRjHv.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tabak">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/FhBKgzt.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tabakH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/vZKRxSe.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yemeniciler">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/pSGFrHn.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="yemenicilerH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/lB2gL1A.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="demirciler">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/mw9advH.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="demircilerH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/Tlw1Sim.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="koprulu">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/8JJVlJ4.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/25M22FM.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/WNXrnsS.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/eL74utd.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/EvB4jwN.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/nsGGijF.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/4OhFbQ0.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/MFFZc4G.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/WluQ4eT.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/v0MCQ6D.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/QPaHFsk.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/kFjG3N5.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/7mJC9yd.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/P68Pr6a.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/bGHUky0.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="kopruluH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/ZMXcp3t.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/ZM0oaTM.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/5JzzQqN.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/HAT4R4j.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/BY1Yq4H.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/E97CVpy.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/ZFqBdNG.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/XVC7v4s.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/Esf7IlA.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/A2uDqn5.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/T3V9PHx.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/Ym7Qq2g.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/l7lebNp.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/WF5Cm1G.jpg</item>
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/hnIMyLc.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eskibel">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/hnGDYqA.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="eskibelH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/hnGDYqA.png</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="camteras">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/7Xmd7Rg.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="camterasH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/fdCpW98.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ulucamii">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/EUlUpVp.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ulucamiiH">
        <item>https://i.imgur.com/hiEdZM5.jpg</item>
    </string-array>

<!--    END HERE-->






































    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tanitim_metni1">
        Safranbolu takes visitors on a historical journey with its unspoilt historical texture and houses.

    </string>
    <string name="tanitim_metni2">
        Safranbolu, one of the first values of Turkey to be included in the UNESCO World Heritage List, has been on this list since 1994.

    </string>
    <string name="tanitim_metni3">
        Safranbolu, which gained its current structure in the 17th and 18th centuries, draws attention with its quality that developed in accordance with the Turkish city structure, depending on time and needs, growing by adding to each other, adapting to nature and protecting it.
    </string>
    <string name="gridTitle">
        ALL LANDMARKS
    </string>
    <string name="map">
        Map
    </string>
    <string name="mapStyle">
        Map Style
    </string>
    <string name="mapStyleDefault">
        Standard
    </string>
    <string name="altitude">
        Altitude
    </string>
    <string name="geofence">
        Geofence
    </string>
    <string name="geofenceRadius">
        Geofence Radius
    </string>
    <string name="playVideosIn">
        Play videos in
    </string>
    <string name="appLanguage">
        App Language
    </string>















    <string name="title_activity_settings">SettingsActivity</string>






















    <!-- Preference Titles -->
    <string name="messages_header">Messages</string>
    <string name="sync_header">Sync</string>

    <!-- Messages Preferences -->
    <string name="signature_title">Your signature</string>
    <string name="reply_title">Default reply action</string>

    <!-- Sync Preferences -->
    <string name="sync_title">Sync email periodically</string>
    <string name="attachment_title">Download incoming attachments</string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_on">Automatically download attachments for incoming emails
    </string>
    <string name="attachment_summary_off">Only download attachments when manually requested</string>
    <string name="title_activity_details">DetailsActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_video">VideoActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="title_activity_image">ImageActivity</string>
</resources>
